[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which species has the most complex color vision system in the animal kingdom?", "correct_answer": "Mantis shrimp", "incorrect_answers": ["Honey- and bumblebees", "Fat-tailed dunnart", "Pigeons"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This science studies signs, both individually and grouped in sign systems.", "correct_answer": "Semiology", "incorrect_answers": ["Anthology", "Linguistics", "Theology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Joe Pantoliano and Carrie-Anne Moss starred together in Memento and this sci-fi classic.", "correct_answer": "The Matrix", "incorrect_answers": ["The Terminator", "The Abyss", "War of The Worlds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What decade was Andy Dufresne sent to the Shawshank prison in the movie The Shawshank Redemption?", "correct_answer": "1940s", "incorrect_answers": ["1920s", "1930s", "1950s"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1992 there was a petition signed by 30,000 people to change the name of Maui, Hawaii to Gilligan.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If your pencil has a pinkish grain and little or no smell, then it is probably made from which substance?", "correct_answer": "plastic", "incorrect_answers": ["incense-cedar", "tropical rainforest wood", "non-incense-cedar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Shining, what was the last name of Jack and Wendy ?", "correct_answer": "Torrence", "incorrect_answers": ["Hannigan", "Charleston", "King"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At this stage of the plague, one of the the symptoms is the presence of black patches on the skin.", "correct_answer": "Septicemic Plague", "incorrect_answers": ["Plague of Justinian", "Pneumonic Plague", "Bubonic Plague"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish the line from Back to the Future character Doc: I remember when this was all farmland as far as the eye could see. Old man Peabody owned all of this. He had this crazy idea about __ __ __.", "correct_answer": "breeding pine trees", "incorrect_answers": ["uprooting pine trees", "enlarging pine trees", "mutating pine trees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did Richard Gere almost get arrested in India in 2007?", "correct_answer": "For behaving improperly", "incorrect_answers": ["For swearing on TV", "For wearing shorts in public", "For asking where he could have a beef steak"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which two famous ghosts supposedly haunt the Hollywood Roosevelt Hotel?", "correct_answer": "Marilyn Monroe and Montgomery Clift.", "incorrect_answers": ["Douglas Fairbanks and Mary Pickford.", "Frank Sinatra and Ava Gardner.", "Laurel and Hardy."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The extrapyramidal system in human brain, which consists of related neurons is not responsible for what?", "correct_answer": "The aural memory", "incorrect_answers": ["Decrease of the erratic motions", "Muscle tone", "Stability of the human body"]}]